(Sheldon:)We happen to live in
a golden age of television.
-Excuse me, fellas.
Sorry for eavesdropping,
but there actually was
some big string theory news today
out of the Hadron Collider.
(Sheldon:)Really?
Did they find evidence to support
(Sheldon:)extra dimensions
or supersymmetry?
(Barry:)No, but they did find evidence
that you'll believe anything.
(Sheldon:)Why would you do that?
(Sheldon:)You're a string theorist as well.
Incorrect.
I am a string pragmatist.
I say I'm gonna prove something
that cannot be proved,
I apply for grant money,
(Barry:)and then I spend it
on liquor and broads.
(Howard:)Later.
(Sheldon:)Do you think he's right?
(Sheldon:)Am I wasting my life on a theory
that can never be proven?
(Howard:)Maybe. But how great
is Game of Thrones?